Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/hoi-nguyena1a5a774 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Software Testing
API Testing
Analytical Skills

Hoi Nguyen

Senior Software Tester

Vietnam

Summary

I am a hard-working, reliable, dedicated and proactive individual who enjoys working in a team or alone. I have over several years experience as a Microsoft Office tester, working on both the client-server and web-based software. As a manual tester, I tested functional, integration, regression, non-functional, stress, performance and acceptance scenarios on multiple projects

Experience

FPT Software
Senior Software Tester
July 2018 - Present (6 years 9 months)
Da Nang City, Vietnam

Công ty Dịch thuật chất lượng cao English Translator January 2016 - May 2023 (7 years 5 months) Da nang

LogiGear Corporation Senior Tester July 2017 - July 2018 (1 year 1 month) da nang

Gameloft Senior Game Tester October 2013 - June 2017 (3 years 9 months) Da nang

OTC Receptionist 2011 - 2013 (2 years)

Education

Danang University of Foreign Languages

Bachelor's degree, English Language and Literature/Letters · (2007 - 2011)